Slater Company Records
© 2004 University of Connecticut
- Series VIII: General Accounts, 1818-1892
  - Ledgers
    - 1832 - 1849 (Box 58)
    - 1858 - 1878
    - 1892
  - Journals
    - 1832 - 1848 (Box 59)
    - 1858 - 1872 (Box 60)
    - Daily account book, 1891 - 1893
  - Cash books
    - 1825 - 1845 (Box 61)
    - 1847 - 1852 (Box 62)
    - 1857 - 1876 (Box 63)
    - Cash blotter, 1831 - 1833
    - Cash memo, 1830 - 1831
    - Cashbook, 1876 - 1884 (Box 64)
  - Order books
    - 1873 - 1874
    - 1874 - 1876 (Box 65)
    - 1876 - 1877 (Box 66)
    - 1882 - 1885
    - 1883 - 1886 (Box 67)
    - n. d. (Box 68)
    - Receipt book, 1827 - 1842 (Box 69)
    - Commissions and ledger accounts, 1846 - 1851
  - Daybooks
    - 1838 - 1840 (Box 71)
    - 1840 (Box 72)
    - 1840 - 1841 (Box 73)
    - 1841 - 1843 (Box 74)
    - 1843 - 1844 (Box 75)
    - 1857 - 1858 (Box 76)
    - 1858 - 1859 (Box 77)
    - 1860 (Box 78)
    - 1860 - 1861 (Box 79)
    - 1861 - 1863 (Box 80)
    - 1863 - 1866 (Box 81)
    - 1866 - 1868 (Box 82)
    - 1867 - 1869 (Box 83)
    - 1868 - 1870 (Box 84)
    - 1870 - 1871 (Box 85)
    - 1871 - 1872 (Box 86)
    - 1872 - 1873 (Box 87)
    - 1873 - 1875 (Box 88)
    - 1875 - 1876 (Box 89)
    - 1876 - 1878 (Box 90)
    - 1877 - 1878 (Box 91)
    - 1878 (Box 92)
    - 1879 - 1880 (Box 93)
    - 1879 - 1880 (Box 94)
    - 1880 - 1881 (Box 95)
    - 1880 - 1881 (Box 96)
    - 1881 - 1882 (Box 97)
    - 1881 - 1882 (Box 98)
    - 1886 - 1888 (Box 99)
    - 1888 - 1890 (Box 100)
  - Blotters
    - 1826 - 1832 (Box 101)
    - 1832 - 1838 (Box 102)
    - 1837 - 1840 (Box 103)
    - 1840 - 1841 (Box 104)
    - 1840 - 1841 (Box 105)
    - 1841 - 1842 (Box 106)
    - 1842 - 1843 (Box 107)
    - 1843 - 1845 (Box 108)
    - 1845 - 1849 (Box 109)
    - 1848 - 1851 (Box 110)
    - 1850 - 1852 (Box 111)
    - 1852 - 1857 (Box 112)
    - Expense account and inventories, 1838 - 1840 (Box 113)
    - Inventories, 1840, 1843 - 1844
    - Balance sheets, 1885 - 1887
- Series IX: Family Account Books, 1850-1890
  - Volumes
    - A - B (Box 114)
    - B (Box 115 - 117)
    - B - C (Box 118)
    - C (Box 119)
    - C - D (Box 120)
    - D - F (Box 121)
    - F (Box 122)
    - F - G (Box 123)
    - G (Box 124)
    - G - H (Box 125)
    - H (Box 126)
    - H - K (Box 127)
    - K - L (Box 128)
    - L - M (Box 129)
    - M (Box 130-132)
    - M - O (Box 133)
    - O - P (Box 134)
    - P - R (Box 135)
    - R (Box 136)
    - S (Box 137)
    - S - T (Box 138)
    - T - V (Box 139)
    - W (Box 140)
    - W - Z, unidentified (Box 141)
- HOPEVILLE MILL AND STORE, 1828-1845
- Series X: Store Records, 1828-1843
  - Daybooks
    - 1828 - 1829 (Box 142)
    - 1829 (Box 143)
    - 1829 - 1830 (Box 144)
    - 1830 - 1831 (Box 145)
    - 1831 - 1833 (Box 146)
    - 1833 - 1836 (Box 147)
    - 1841 - 1843 (Box 148)
    - Blotter, 1829 - 1830
- Series XI: Mill Records, 1829-1845
  - Cashbook, 1837 - 1838 (Box 149)
  - Invoice book, 1841 - 1842
  - Receipt book, 1829 - 1838
  - Baleing book, 1841 - 1845
  - Weaving book, 1841 - 1845
  - Supply accounts, 1841 - 1845 (Box 150)
  - Time book and production, 1829 - 1845